<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
 	<channel>
		<title>Kazakhstan | Bike From Beijing to Paris | Deray</title>
		<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/</link>
		<description></description>
		<language>zh-Hant</language>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 17:18:55 +0800</lastBuildDate>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<generator>Sandvox 2.10.12</generator>
		<item>
			<title>Takeshi Kitano Border</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0720.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;The weather was changeable, dry to wet, and wet to dry, and switched rapidly. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was sunny at one moment, but poured the next minute.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I stayed in my hotel room, watching Takeshi Kitano movies the whole day. Good movies enriched my rest days.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Today, I watched ‘Kikujiro’s Summer’ about a boy living with his grandmother looked for his mother during summer vacation.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Less than one hour after setting out, he is extorted for money by bad kids. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It turns out that he is accompanied by an irresponsible man (who is worse than the bad kids) to look for his mom. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Many things happen along the way. The story is quite long and not simply about looking for mom. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The movie has Kitano’s unique style, super funny but very touching.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/vlcsnap-1008972_med-2.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="480" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In addition, I watched ‘Dolls’ which is one of only a few movies directed by Takeshi Kitano without himself playing in the movie.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three love stories are woven together in the movie. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The red rope fate story connects the entire movie, and the other two stories were just side stories.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 20 Jul 2007 22:11:02 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0720.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-90_hr.jpeg" length="8868" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Just Wait a Little Bit Longer</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0719.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;Took off for one day, I was so fully “charged”, like the Chinese said, “I started the wind when I am on the move”. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yes, that was how good I felt about myself today.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During those days in China, I got to take my time off every couple of days. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But in Kazakhstan, I finally could take one day off after biking for more than 20 days.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, I didn’t bike as long distance everyday here as I did in China, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;so I guessed I was not that tired- unless I couldn’t get a good night sleep. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I didn’t want to pay too much for breakfast, so I usually made a 700cc hot coffee using my own water bottle, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;and drank that with 10 loaves of bread. Everything together was under 100 tengs.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Eating the breakfast and packing at the same time,
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I thought I should be able to reach the border by today, and I wondered what that would look like.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was guessing, many trucks waiting in line? Probably not. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because the border here opens 24 hours a day, the line can’t be too long. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I did hope, though, that I could find a little town there. A little town with restaurant, stores and hotels. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 19 Jul 2007 22:11:01 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0719.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-89_hr.jpeg" length="10647" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Soaking Wet</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0713.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;It has been cloudy or raining these days. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sometime it was drizzling, and sometime I got soaking wet in the rain.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Back to back rainy days depressed me.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I woke up this morning, the sky was terribly overcast. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If my raincoat was still with me, I would put it on before the rain started, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;because a heavy rainstorm could burst out the next second.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Without knowing where my raincoat was, I had better ride out of the cloudy area as far and fast as I could.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1100010_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before I set out, Rustan came on a bike to see me off. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He escorted me riding to the fork road outside the town and said good bye to me
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rain started since then and never stopped the entire day.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1100012_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Here the road was under construction with a detour sign. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I rode here yesterday, I got frustrated enough to stop. However I still had to start from here today.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I did not want to get on the temporary road, following the tire tracks in the dirt, and riding on the road still under construction.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1100014_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The condition of the road under construction was much better than the temporary road. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 13 Jul 2007 22:10:54 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0713.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-83_hr.jpeg" length="15128" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>A Secret Hideout</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0712.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;It rained last night so that everywhere was wet when I woke up in the morning. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even the air was wet, as if the fish can just jump out and swim in the air. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My breakfast was two cups of coffee, two meat-filled pancakes, and two eggs, thank to the night-shift guys in the hotel.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1090890_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was ready to bike for today right after finishing the breakfast. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The wind was much better compared to what I had encountered yesterday. We were having a gentle breeze today.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;About one hour later, I saw a city appeared in the fog. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I seemed to see a tall building standing there, looked like a well-developed area. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;With the hope of finding the internet, I detoured immediately to search for this city.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1090898_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, when I physically arrived there, I found the “tall building” was just a regular factory; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the whole city was just another regular city I had seen in Kazakhstan. Well, just a short detour, no big deal. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1090900_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wait a minute. What was wrong with me? 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I detoured to this city because I THOUGHT there was internet available here, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 12 Jul 2007 22:04:39 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0712.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-82_hr.jpeg" length="17072" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Friendship on Wrist</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0706.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;I was not too sure if Granny and Sartana got up early to cooperate with me. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was about to wash up, and my tent was not packed up yet when they got out of bed.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I greeted granny with “good morning” in Chinese. Woops! 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Perhaps it was too homey and relaxing, I forgot that I was in Kazakhstan.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Breakfast was hot milk tea, hot coffee and bread – simple but tasty.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sartana was busy getting a bunch of crackers on the table saying that granny wanted me to carry them on the road.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had seen the same crackers in restaurants and also bought some in grocery stores myself. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They were not cheap. They gave me four bags with different flavors.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;They did not charge me for breakfast and the crackers. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I quietly tucked a small 200 KZT bill in Sartana’s pocket as her allowance.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1090177_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Right before I left, Sartana kept saying “labanmi” “labanmi” to me. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;New word, never heard of it. She pointed her necklace and bracelet. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Did she mean to exchange souvenirs?
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It reminded me of Kepa where I stayed one night a few days ago. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 06 Jul 2007 22:04:30 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0706.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-76_hr.jpeg" length="14006" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Sleeping like a baby</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0705.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;I woke up at dawn. I didn’t sleep well. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I spent the entire night closing my eyes and volunteering my blood to the mosquito inside my personal tent.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the record, I had more than 40 mosquito bites all over my body. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was applying the mentholatum (we used a lot in Taiwan for little bit of everything) 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;and found myself basically rubbing that all over my two arms.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The experience I encountered yesterday slowed down my brain function, so it took me a while to reset my priority. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Bu the sudden tummy ache reminded me that I also had diarrhea and vomiting symptom too.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1090126_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Therefore, the first thing now was to find a restroom. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was lucky enough to know that god has not abandoned me yet.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He gave me a gas station and a quiet space to clean up my body.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My body ached, and tired, and I still had to repack everything. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had no energy nor mood to check if anything, other than my cell phone, was missing.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had vomited pretty much everything yesterday, and I couldn’t make myself to eat anything now. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 05 Jul 2007 22:04:29 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0705.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-75_hr.jpeg" length="17877" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Village Hill</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0702.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;After a delightful shower, I had a good sleep in this comfortable room. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the morning, I acted as a little child - didn’t want to get out of bed; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I didn’t know when I will have a chance to sleep on a bed again.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;        Taking this infrequently resource again after got out of the bad, I took a shower one more time. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Next few days I probably won’t have any chance to take any shower.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After packaged my stuff, I saw the restaurant was being opened. The restaurant is opened for breakfast also.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;        I walked to kitchen directly to see what kind of food I liked that was faster and convenience comparing looked at menu. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There was sound coming from a pan; the chef was frying meat in a pan; the air was filled with delicacies smell.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;        I pointed to the pan; I wanted to have this, gave it to me, gave it to me.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1080741_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;        The owner also cooked 2 eggs and took a big bottle of apple juice from the refrigerator. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I hadn’t this type of food, including breads, for a long time.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;        Besides ate my owner food, I also looked others food from tables around me.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 02 Jul 2007 21:55:10 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0702.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-72_hr.jpeg" length="8086" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The priority of my desires</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0701.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;Sleep quite well last night. The snack bar closes very late, while the noise of guests coming for food could be heard even on 2 or 3 am. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is really hard to do this business for such bars by the roadside.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I woke up I felt my body is fully printed by the spring bed, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;and some joints just felt being dislocated and relocated again. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I carried my towel and toothbrush to wash up. Above the washbasin in front of the shop, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;there were three dragonfly-like and two moth-like insects floating on the water tank. I stared for three seconds.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And I decided to pretend not seeing these bathing insects, and still wash up using this water. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When in Rome, do as Romans do. If I don’t adapt myself to it, how to live in Kazakhstan from now on?
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1080651_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The water in the bottle I prepared to drink today came from that the snack bar boiled for making tea. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Actually the un-boiled water here maybe basically not for drinking, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;but people don’t care and just drink it since the source of water is very few here.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 01 Jul 2007 21:55:09 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0701.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-71_hr.jpeg" length="11494" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Manager in Decaying Kepa</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0629.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;It rained for the whole night last night, but stopped when I got up at dawn. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Cars on the road made a sound of water splashing when swooshing by.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though the heavy rain had stopped, water puddles were everywhere.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last night I slept in Nemat’s dorm room, a tiny place with two beds, one desk, and walls full of beauty posters from magazines.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1080220_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the early morning everybody was still asleep. The iron gate of the restaurant was locked, and so was Dido. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I managed to find a person sleeping in the storage room to unlock Dido.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Getting Dido back and changing clothes, I was asked if I would like to eat something or drink some tea.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at my watch, it was still quite early. Everybody was either still asleep or not at work yet. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In order not to trouble anyone, I decided to eat along the road later.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1080219_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;While doing my nightly routine before sleep, I found my toothbrush and toothpaste were gone. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I recollected that they were left on the sink vanity in the hotel room where I stayed the day before yesterday.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 29 Jun 2007 21:55:07 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0629.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-69_hr.jpeg" length="13851" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Car City</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0628.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;Flies were everywhere in Kazakhstan, and they were getting on my nerves. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even when I finally got myself a comfy bed, I had to win the patient contest with the flies before I can sleep in it.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;During the day, the flies kept me company on my bike. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I couldn’t wave them away all the time because I did need to care for my own safety on the road.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wearing the clothes that I just washed yesterday, I was ready to have my breakfast and leave. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This was a rather simple meal, some bread and a pot of milk tea (maybe 6 cups?). I like my milk tea VERY sweet, by adding two
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;cubes of sugar for each cup. I liked to watch the cubes of sugar gradually dissolved into the tea, very entertaining.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I should be able to arrive at the old capital city, which was less than 40 km away, around noon. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was hoping that I could find this place that somebody gave me the information about. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Then I could spend the night there, and/or get online, or even some one will take me for dinner, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I also would like to buy a map, exchange the currency, etc. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 28 Jun 2007 21:55:06 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0628.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-68_hr.jpeg" length="16888" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>How do you spell HOTEL in Kazakh</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0627.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;Wow! Not even 5 o’clock in the morning, I had already gotten up, climbed out of my tent, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;which had no insulation effect whatsoever. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I washed my face with the freezing water, and found my eyes bags were as big as walnuts, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;thanks to those “sleepless” truck drivers.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I went into the restaurant and found that waitress had the same eyes bags like mine.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thanks for her kindness; she brought me a pot of hot milk tea, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;which warmed me up from my heart to every single part of my body.  And she even refused to let me pay for it. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I filled up my three water bottles before took off. It was really a great thing to travel in a country that tap water is drinkable. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I remembered when I biked in France, I might not pay attention to all the beautiful scenery in that country, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;but the instinct of looking for drinking water never failed me.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1070993_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I should get going now, 6:30 in the morning. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was better to leave early, plus the weather was cooler, I hoped I can keep this good habit.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was downhill after leaving Koback (phonetic translation), 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 27 Jun 2007 21:55:04 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0627.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-67_hr.jpeg" length="14634" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Across the border</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0625.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;I can't believe that this one month bike trip in Kazakhstan got me sleepless. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I rolled on the bed and finally fall at sleep when the sun is about to rise.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It feels like at the moment I fall at sleep, the alarm of my watch starts beeping. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I totally want to stay in bed for some more time, but it will not be possible today.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After using the bathroom, I take my bags and Dido downstairs. Since I have all my bags packed before I sleep, this doesn't take much time. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I took off with the greeting from the owner of the hotel, under the morning sunshine at half pass six. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1070630_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In half an hour I rode 7 kilometers on Dido, and arrived at Huoerguosi. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;As usual, all the trucks are still waiting in the long line at the "national gate", 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;which is the nickname of the border gate from the locals. However, unlike my previous visits,the border gate will open today. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Therefore the gate is crowded with people. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1070633_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All kind of people surrounds me right after I stopped with Dido. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That includes currency exchange guy, begging old lady, chatter box and the bell boys. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 25 Jun 2007 21:55:02 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/kazakhstan/0625.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-65_hr.jpeg" length="21122" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
 	</channel>
</rss>