<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
 	<channel>
		<title>Germany | Bike From Beijing to Paris | Deray</title>
		<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/germany/</link>
		<description></description>
		<language>zh-Hant</language>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 17:19:00 +0800</lastBuildDate>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<generator>Sandvox 2.10.12</generator>
		<item>
			<title>Rule of the cyclist</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/germany/0908.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-143_hr.jpeg" alt="" width="250" height="180" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;I kept thinking today is Sunday, so I thought no one would wake up early for work, so I let myself sleep until 7am.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I slept soundly in the tent for 9 hours, then I wondered how come it is very loud outside, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;after getting out of the tent I realized it was Saturday today. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I estimate I will arrive at my destination on September 12, 2008, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;counting the days, if lucky; it will be in Paris next Wednesday.  Then the long trip will end.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1180784_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once I start missing home the time starts to pass slowly, if not counting today, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;just count from the Germany/France border, just 3.5 more days riding to Paris.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is scary counting the days backwards.  After collecting all my things, this is my last day in Germany. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It is hard to determine whether today’s weather is good or bad, but at least it didn’t start raining when I got up.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But the clouds are covered with dark clouds, just the same as every other day. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though I had though I need to hurry to finish the last day in Germany, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;but after studying the map last night I found I am not very far from the border, but I had thought I am in the middle of Germany.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 08 Sep 2007 22:54:53 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/germany/0908.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1180786_med-3.jpeg" length="128295" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Peter’s Home</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/germany/0906.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;By the time I moved everything up to the second floor and placed everything for the night,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I found there is a window that leads to the street,and the window doesn’t have any glass on it.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This means if there is someone that comes in here in the middle of the night, they can easily get into this house. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;For safety reason, I purposely found some wood sticks and blocks off the window.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So if someone comes in they will hit those wood sticks, and wakes me up from my sleep.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The safety procedure is just in case, good thing the whole night was fine, slept until morning. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1180576_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Outside ground is a bit wet; maybe there is some rain last night.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;By the time the sun came up today, it had stopped raining, and seems like the weather today is much better than the last few days.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Since I can get out from the second floor, there is no need to move the bike to the downstairs area. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I can get out from the 2nd floor window; just one trip takes care of it all.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1180577_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I left this empty house, walking to the quiet neighborhood, it was still very quiet around 7:30am, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 06 Sep 2007 22:54:51 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/germany/0906.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-141_hr.jpeg" length="11475" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
 	</channel>
</rss>