<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
 	<channel>
		<title>Russia | Bike From Beijing to Paris | Deray</title>
		<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/russia/</link>
		<description></description>
		<language>zh-Hant</language>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 17:18:57 +0800</lastBuildDate>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<generator>Sandvox 2.10.12</generator>
		<item>
			<title>Excellent Leg Strength</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/russia/0803.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;I woke up with a headache. It was a mild cold caused by the combination &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;of the cold night temperature and the moisture trapped inside the tent. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I should be able to recover after sunbathing.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;The positive way to see it was there was no need to pack my sleeping bag after getting out of bed. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The lazy plan made me feel relaxed.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I felt like sponge cleaning my face before I set off, however only juice and brown sugar water were in my bottles. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those were not good for face washing.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I used the damp towel which I had already used to clean my body yesterday to roughly wipe my face, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;then my washing routine in the morning was done – 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;kids who do not like washing and brushing their teeth after getting out of bed can follow me!
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had a choice to make after I left the campsite under the bridge. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Should I return to the rest area where I passed by yesterday and look for a restaurant to eat and get washed at, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;or should I continue on till the next rest area showed up?
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I picked out the later simply because I had to ride uphill if I went back, which upset me just by thinking about it. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 03 Aug 2007 22:24:04 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/russia/0803.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-104_hr.jpeg" length="14428" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>In Bright Daylight</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/russia/0727.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;Sleeping intermittently in the abandoned house, on the whole, it was not bad.&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At night, somebody pulled off the road, and came over to pee next to the house. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The sound of him walking woke me up. I sat up in the tent, looked outside, and saw a peeing shadow.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He was even more startled than I was when he saw someone in the empty house. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It was not fun to frighten each other like that. I wanted to get more sleep if possible.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There were several advantages of camping, such as no need to keep my eyes open to write up travel logs, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;to take a shower, and to do my laundry. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Also, some money could be saved. That made me feel I had achieved something.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When my alarm went off, the passing cars made the sound of water swooshing. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It had rained again last night. Luckily, it had stopped at dawn.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, a rain cloud was still lingering in the sky. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It should have been sunrise around 8:00am, however it just looked like it was before daybreak.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The temperature always remained around 20 degrees C before noon, and then it worked its way up. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 27 Jul 2007 22:17:11 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/russia/0727.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-97_hr.jpeg" length="19088" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
 	</channel>
</rss>