<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
 	<channel>
		<title>Poland | Bike From Beijing to Paris | Deray</title>
		<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/</link>
		<description></description>
		<language>zh-Hant</language>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 17:18:57 +0800</lastBuildDate>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<generator>Sandvox 2.10.12</generator>
		<item>
			<title>Good-Bye, Poland</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0831.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-135_hr.jpeg" alt="" width="250" height="180" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;Just a little past 7am, Goose left for school.  I was just waking up then.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I waved to him for good-bye.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Time for breaks goes by so fast; I felt I had just arrived at Pozana yesterday afternoon with the sun setting behind me.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am leaving Pozana early this morning; I am a bit reluctant to leave.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I stayed here for almost a week, there are a lot more places worth visiting that I haven’t gone yet.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Poland also has other beautiful cities worth visiting; hopefully I will get to come back later in the future.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1170613_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goose posted a message for me on the door; it says 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;“Deray, Have a safe trip.  Bye, Good Luck.” 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I turned the paper over, Goose wrote a big “GO” on the back.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have traveled for more than 4 months now; I am beginning to miss my home. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I want to go home now.  I am thinking about my semi-chaotic room, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the kitchen I can cook in, and the adorable Misasa. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In one trip, I picked up and took all my stuff downstairs to the garage Dido was parked.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I found a postcard from Gorilla in the rear clamp of Dido.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 31 Aug 2007 22:46:36 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0831.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1170624_med-3.jpeg" length="146233" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Mucha over a hundred years ago</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0830.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;I had walked at lot while at the zoo yesterday.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So today, other than going to Mucha’s art exhibit later in the afternoon, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I plan to stay in the dorm all day.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Before I left for the art exhibit, I planned out which route I need to take for the rest of the trip from Germany to Paris.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I decided I am not going to pass through Netherlands and Belgium this time.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In reality, I can still go through those 2 countries, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;which adds 2 more countries to my list of the ones I have already passed.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, unlike Taiwan tourist groups, which uses the number of passing by countries as an advertisement.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I feel quality is better than quantity.  Both Netherlands and Belgium are beautiful countries. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Riding my bike, I can pass those countries in about 2-3 days.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But I wouldn’t be able to enjoy the beautiful scenery along the way.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Rather than passing by quickly this time, I would rather take time on future trips to really enjoy those countries.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the route I plan to take:
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/ge3_med-2.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="564" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I plan to take 1-2 days to ride to the Poland and Germany border.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 30 Aug 2007 22:46:35 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0830.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-134_hr.jpeg" length="10239" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Animals at the Zoo</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0829.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-133_hr.jpeg" alt="" width="250" height="180" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;I left early today carrying a backpack containing 2 bottles of water, some chocolate biscuits, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;map, and a camera.  I am going to Poznan’s zoo today.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is only one restaurant in the zoo and a store selling zoo merchandise.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, I don’t need to ask to know that the price at the zoo will be expensive.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Whatever I need I will bring on my own.  I got the map from the visitor’s center.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bus ticket was bought previously.  I also got the map that Goose drew for me. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It contains the direction from the dorm to the bus stop, which bus I need to take, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;and how I get from the bus stop to the train station.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1170130_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I passed by bunch of couples in love on my way walking from the dorm to the bus stop.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though I am by myself, I am determined to enjoy myself on this trip.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1170133_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The bus stop across the street is where I will need to board the cable car. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I need to take number 6 cable car.  I will pass by 6 stops, total about 24 minutes.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Therefore, I need 2 tickets with 10 minutes each for the 30 minute trip.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 29 Aug 2007 22:46:33 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0829.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1170349_med-3.jpeg" length="322370" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Dorm Dweller Goes Out</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0828.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-132_hr.jpeg" alt="" width="250" height="180" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;Ever since arriving to Goose’s dorm,&lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have stayed in completely in the room browsing the internet and writing the travel diaries. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I didn’t leave the dorm at all on August 27th.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The travel diaries from August 27th are actually the travel from the afternoon of August 26th.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;That night the Poznana student from Taiwan cooked a scrumptious meal for me to eat.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The person who cooked the meal for me was too busy to eat, they had to go back to study for their test.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is so sad. T_T
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1160931_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Three Cup Chicken and Curry are great; the meal also supplemented my lack of vegetables from previous meals.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If you have friends who are Indian, then they would look down upon you for using curry seasoning cubs to make curry. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It doesn’t matter as long as the flavor is great.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The weather wasn’t good that night, dark clouds were very low and dark.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The cold breeze at night makes the temperature keep going down.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Does this mean the few good weather days will end?
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1160924_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After I got up, it was still blue skies.  Good thing it didn’t rain or I would stay in the dorm for another day.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 28 Aug 2007 22:46:32 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0828.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1170090_med-3.jpeg" length="176693" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Solemn and Respectful Big Church</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0827.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-131_hr.jpeg" alt="" width="250" height="180" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;The biggest problem has been solved in Poland, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;after both the front and the rear tires of the bike were changed.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;All that are left are just small things that need to be fixed; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goose and Guerilla together fixed the rest of the problems.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1160594_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Because of my stupidity, I forgot to unplug a wire on the bike when I changed the tires. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I kept wondering why the front tire wouldn’t come off, was it caught on something?  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So after my very hard pull, the wire that connects the night-light on the bike was broken.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The wire has been broken for over a month,
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I didn’t want to mention this since I was afraid people would worry 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;about me and I coudln’t fix this wire immediately. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I was pretty sure I would hear lots of concerned comments about 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;riding at night without any lights to guide me.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1160575_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So I know I have to find a resting place everyday before nightfall, and not ride in the dark.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I have been safe all the way so far, and finally I can ride normally with everything fixed.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Guerilla connects the positive and the negative wires back, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 27 Aug 2007 22:46:31 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0827.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1160692_med-3.jpeg" length="212048" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Nothing Is Strange Anymore</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0826.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-130_hr.jpeg" alt="" width="250" height="180" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;Today is Sunday, the second rest day in Poznana.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In my original plan, I had planned to leave Poznana tomorrow.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the plan has changed, this city is worth to be walked around, I am in no hurry to leave.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thus this has become one of the days I am in Poznana.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Poznana is a quiet city anyway, and on Sunday it is even quieter.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is only the church bell heard on the street since everyone has gone to the Sunday church service.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In this city with lots of churches around, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I randomly picked a church near the old city to observe the Sunday service.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1160438_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="1600" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This church looks very simple outside, but it is breath taking beautiful inside.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The place is filled with people coming for the Sunday service, and all the seats are gone.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The people that are just entering will have to stand for the service.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is a little boy dressed in black sitting on a stool by the front entrance reading a book.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;His clothing are clean and elegant, it is hard to imagine he is actually a beggar.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The beggar in Poznana has high class.  They stand quietly on the street side, and most are clean.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 26 Aug 2007 22:46:30 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0826.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1160482_med-3.jpeg" length="224184" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>The Old City, Still With Its Glory</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0825.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;The soft bed is here again, changing between camping and comfortable surroundings.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After leaving MSI’s dorm in Moscow, I camped for another seven days before I reached Poland boarder.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the boarder I stayed in another hotel to be freshened and energized.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After entering Poland it was another 3 days of camping.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Lying on the bed thinking about the places I have camped, I have camped at various places.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The nicest place I slept in was the abandoned house, the most interesting was the middle of the field, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;and the worst was when I got kicked out when I was half asleep.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is just 2000km (1243miles) left to the trip, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;it can easily be accomplished in 15 days as long as I watch for my own safety.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Once I enter Europe, it will be toward the end of the trip.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;If someone asks me how do I feel after traveling alone for over 100 days?
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The people I met on the road said all said “you crazy?” followed by unbelievable looks on their face.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the just harvested field, nothing in sight, thinking how about camping here for the night, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sat, 25 Aug 2007 22:46:29 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0825.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-129_hr.jpeg" length="13404" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Goose, I am Coming!</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0824.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;In one breath, I slept three days worth.  Regardless how loud the rain sounded, it couldn’t fight my sleepyness. &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I fell deep into sleep, the kind of sleep where you don’t realize where you are when you wake up.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The rain stopped early in the morning, although there were still some 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;dark clouds covering the sky so it seems like it might rain again.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Goose called this morning and said it will rain today, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;and all I can wish is it won’t rain anymore so I can ride safely to Poznana.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though rain has stopped, but there is still one annoying thing, the wind is blowing very hard.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The wind is blowing in opposite to the direction I am traveling, so the whole day I rode against the wind.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I kept thinking the earlier I arrive at Poznana so I can rest comfortably for two days, but it didn’t work that way.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I rode slowly the 150Km (93 miles) to Poznana.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had planned to arrive at Poznana in the afternoon, however by the time I arrived at Poznana it was close to dark.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1150900_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The Red #2 freeway I had been on for half of Poland is now under reconstruction.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Fri, 24 Aug 2007 22:46:27 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0824.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-128_hr.jpeg" length="17541" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Light everywhere</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0823.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-127_hr.jpeg" alt="" width="250" height="180" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;After leaning against the uneven wall all night to sleep, &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;it felt there were pricks picking on me.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Around 2am, I got up and changed to sleep on the cold floor, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;and used the sleeping bag as a pillow. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I slept to around 5am and then got up.  This is because of time difference; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the alarm clock woke me up an hour early. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;At the same moment, there was an early rising grandmother who walked out of the apartment. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The grandmother was shocked to see me sleeping on the floor.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Not only did she didn’t ask me to leave; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;she asks me if I need to go inside and sleep on the stair steps.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Thank you but no need since it was almost light outside, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;there is still huge distance I need to ride today.  For where to sleep tonight, I will figure it out later.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ripping off a page from the notebook I wrote some thankful words: 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Last night I say need nothing, &lt;br /&gt;Because your smile is everything&lt;br /&gt;Thank you.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I stick it by the stair steps where I slept hoping the nice person will see it.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After being kicked away several times the whole night, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Thu, 23 Aug 2007 22:46:26 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0823.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1150828_med-3.jpeg" length="260248" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Hard Times</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0822.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;I have been adjusting the time on the watch continuously due to time change.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But it seems like the watch got time change problems too since the alarm went off at 5am 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;when it should have gone off at 6am.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had hung the watch on the bike, so when I heard the alarm went off I didn’t know what time it was really.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I felt I had just gone to sleep and now I had to get up again.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Sleeping in the tent I could see what is going on outside,
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the dark sky shows the sun hasn’t came up yet, so I stayed in bed and will get up in a little bit. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I slept for an extra 30 minutes before getting out of the tent.  Looking out of the window, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I see it is foggy outside even though it didn’t rain last night.  I am very lucky I didn’t sleep somewhere in the field last night.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1150577_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Packing my gear up and I said good-bye to the bird underneath the house.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I stretched a bit before getting ready to ride again.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Now taking a look at the watch I realized it is not 6am yet.  I got up too early because of the faulty alarm.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 22 Aug 2007 22:46:25 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0822.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-126_hr.jpeg" length="15110" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Already Got In Trouble And You Still Want To Leave?</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0821.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;Even though the hotel I stayed in doesn’t have internet like I had wanted, but it still give me a good night’s sleep.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I slept until morning and was ready to go through customs.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the last day the visa is good for Belarus, and the first day entering Europe.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The trip started hard and will now get easier since the road condition will be better in Europe.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, I have to make sure I am able to enter Europe first.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I checked out of the hotel in the morning, the employee 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;on duty is different so the price she charged me is also different.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Yesterday they charged me $32USD, but now this guy on duty is charging me $90,000 Belarus Money ($45USD).  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;He asked me if I used the parking lot?  I said I came here on my bike, so she added fee for parking motorcycle.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So first thing in the morning I was already fighting for my rights with the hotel employee.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good thing I still have the piece of paper the person wrote down with the price on it from last night, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;and no charge for bike storage fee either.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 21 Aug 2007 22:45:23 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/poland/0821.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-125_hr.jpeg" length="14539" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
 	</channel>
</rss>