<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/">
 	<channel>
		<title>France | Bike From Beijing to Paris | Deray</title>
		<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/france/</link>
		<description></description>
		<language>zh-Hant</language>
		<lastBuildDate>Fri, 06 Aug 2021 17:19:01 +0800</lastBuildDate>
		<docs>http://blogs.law.harvard.edu/tech/rss</docs>
		<generator>Sandvox 2.10.12</generator>
		<item>
			<title>No hero here</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/france/0912.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-147_hr.jpeg" alt="" width="250" height="180" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;Around 4am in the morning with the wind blowing on me, since I didn’t change so I used the sleeping bag to cover up myself.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But once I leave the sleeping bag I don’t have any extra clothing to put on.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the dark night with the freezing wind blowing directly to my spine, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;the bike handle is covered with the frozen morning dew; it felt so cold holding it.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The water in the water bottle is very precious, but I still pour some out on a towel, and use the towel to wipe my face.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This counts as another shower.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the star covered sky, I stand on the hard ground and felt like the ground is moving.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My body keep leaning to the back, just like I am drunk, can’t stand straight.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Wasn’t just one night no sleep to write the travel journal?  Is the side effect this serious?  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In a moment I will have to ride on the road, this will be ok, right? 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am not able to stand straight, but this doesn’t mean I can’t ride the bike. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I only have to step on the pedals to ride the bike.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1190219_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;In the pitch-black night, I can’t see anything; I don’t know where the moon has gone.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Wed, 12 Sep 2007 23:02:56 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/france/0912.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1190253_med-3.jpeg" length="256932" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>Tomorrow, Paris</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/france/0911.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;Indoor temperature is definitely better, when I woke up this morning; the temperature is around 10C (50F).  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Looking at the temperature I feel better inside, this is better than temperature at single digit.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had felt if I sleep here, people might come in early to work, so I set the alarm up at 6am to wake myself up. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am hoping to leave here early without any noticing me, but the alarm froze so it didn’t ring so I slept until 7am in the morning.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I woke up I quickly packed up the camping gear, I was afraid I would be discovered.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Good thing when I left everything was ok, and the temperature outside was fine too.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The clouds is still dark and dreary, the frozen fingers need some exercise before they would move.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;After I left I remembered why I rode here, it was because of those cars only path.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Those cars only path would still be there, they wouldn’t disappear just after my sleep, so I need to figure out a way to ride on the cars only path.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1190137_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The path I need to take clearly has cars only signs posted.  Of course I can choose to ride on it regardless, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Tue, 11 Sep 2007 23:02:55 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/france/0911.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-146_hr.jpeg" length="11574" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>I Am Slow When Blowing Against Me</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/france/0910.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;My body became stiff from staying the whole night in the little log cabin.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, during the whole night it didn’t rain, but all the stuff that was left outside the log cabin is now covered with the morning dew.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;There is probably something wrong with my watch.  When the watch shows it is not going to rain, it will rain.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;And when the watch shows it will rain, and then it might rain, sometimes even 3 days later.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;When I got up this morning the weather was pretty good, I can still see the pretty sunrise. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1190043_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I went to the water pump I found yesterday and used the near frozen water to wipe my face.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;My hand became numb when I got the towel wet with the cold water.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Using the frozen cold water to rub my face a bit, and now my whole face became numb as well.  Just like this, I am awake.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This is the second day in France, so lets continue to ride. 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I still didn’t ride to 150km yesterday, and I entered from Germany, so I actually rode less than what I had planned.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;So today I need to work hard and make up for yesterday.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Mon, 10 Sep 2007 23:02:53 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/france/0910.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-145_hr.jpeg" length="12377" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
		<item>
			<title>My Secret Weapon</title>
			<link>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/france/0909.html</link>
			<description>
				&lt;div class="article-summary"&gt;&lt;p&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p class="style5"&gt;&lt;span style="background-color: transparent;"&gt;I didn’t take out the sleeping bag or the mattress pad the night before.  &lt;/span&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I just wrapped myself up in the sleeping bag and slept on the bench in front of the store for the night.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;The next morning the guy delivering the paper woke me up.  I didn’t realize I would sleep well like this too.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;It started raining lightly when I was getting ready to leave in the morning.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;This wasn’t a big problem since the rain wasn’t big, besides I have been rained on a lot lately so this little rain doesn’t bother me.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;However, the bike was weird, it felt like it doesn’t want to move.  I bent down to check it and found out the back tire was out of air.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1180892_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="first" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Even though I knew the back tire has problems loosing air, but I thought it was just low pressure.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt; 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;But after I wake up now the whole tire has no air, it looks like someone has let out the air completely.  
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Is it possible something poked it?  I was suspicious, but the probability isn’t high so I still took off the tire and check.
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/p1180895_med-3.jpeg" alt="" width="640" height="506" class="not-first-item" /&gt;
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;I had thought after I changed to the new tire, 
					&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
			</description>
			<pubDate>Sun, 09 Sep 2007 23:02:15 +0800</pubDate>
			<guid>https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/log/france/0909.html</guid>
            <enclosure url="https://derayga.github.io/btp.en/_Media/logo-144_hr.jpeg" length="19088" type="image/jpeg"></enclosure>
			
		</item>
 	</channel>
</rss>